- 你好。
- 谁，我？他？
- Hi.
- Who, me? Him?
- Not you.
- Don't worry about it.
- 不是你。
- 不要担心。
Hey!
嘿！
- How are you doing?
- Oh, fuck off.
- 你怎么样？
- 哦，滚开。
- What's up?
- Feel good. All right.
- 这是怎么回事？
- 感觉不错。好的。
Excuse me.
对不起。
- Yeah. Score.
- Very nice.
- 是啊。分数。
- 很不错的。
好的。让我们来谈谈
这个小老太太叫夜。
All right. Let's talk
to this little lady called Night.
I broke the window again.
我再一次打破了窗口。
- Dad's gonna be pissed.
- I'll just tell him you did it.
- 爸爸会很生气。
- 我就告诉他，你做到了。
But I didn't do it.
I'm driving. Don't do that.
但我没有做到这一点。
我开车。不要那样做。
所以不管怎么说，我站在那里，
等待使用公用电话...
So anyways, I'm standing there,
waiting to use the pay phone...
这家伙在电话里轮流
各地和提示他的帽子是这样的。
And this guy on the phone turns
around and tips his hat like this.
又是谁，你认为那个家伙是？
And who do you think that guy was?
- Emilio Estevez.
- 'The Mighty Duck'. I was there!
- 埃米利奥埃斯特韦斯。
- “全能的鸭子”。我在那里！
当然你。你大叫
在“早餐和Clubber的”名称。
Of course you were. You yelled
the "Breakfast Clubber's" name.
So, anyway.
You guys wanna make out or what?
所以，无论如何。
你们想使出来还是什么？
Oh, man. lt was perfect that time.
哦，伙计。 LT是完美的那段时间。
Four months of work for nothing.
四个月没有工作。
- What's up?
- Did you know you were doing 50?
- 这是怎么回事？
- 你知道你在做什么50？
Hottie cop likes you. Think she pulls
over just anybody? Make a move.
棘手的警察喜欢你。想她拉
在普通的人？做出的举动。
- What's up?
- Just giving you an $80 ticket.
- 这是怎么回事？
- 只是给你80美元的罚单。
She is so into you.
她是那么到你。
- I want you to do me a favor.
- Whatever you say, 'T.J. Hooker".
- 我要你帮我一个忙。
- 无论你说什么，'T.J.妓女“。
请遵守所有张贴的速度限制。
有一个美好的夜晚。
Please obey all posted speed limits.
Have a good night.
It's already been good, now
that you've served and protected me.
它已经被很好的，现在
你已经送达，保护我。
- 什么是那一点？
- 对不起。
- What was the point of that?
- Sorry.
Come next week. I'm gonna
take care of you. All right, man.
下周来吧。我要去
照顾你。好吧，伙计。
This is the Roxbury. We have a list.
这是罗克斯伯里。我们有一个列表。
- 我们的名单上。道格Butabi。
- 史蒂夫Butabi。
- We're on the list. Doug Butabi.
- Steve Butabi.
- 你是兄弟？
- 号
- You're brothers?
- No.
- Yes. Man!
- That's quite a joke.
- 是的。男人！
- 这是相当一个笑话。
- Doug is hilarious.
- Check this out.
- 道格是热闹。
- 检查了这一点。
你听说过这个吗？
你不就行了。取得一致。
You ever heard of this one?
You're not on the list. Get in line.
- LS的..？
- 它是“21跳街”之王。
- ls that..?
- It's the king of "21 Jump Street".
Richard Grieco.
理查德GRIECO。
- Excuse me.
- See you later. We'll go wait in line.
- 对不起。
- 再见。我们会去排队等候。
- Maybe we'll hang out later?
- No chance.
- 也许我们会在后面挂了？
- 没有机会。
- 听起来不错。
- 知道什么是不对的地方吗？
- Sounds good.
- Know what's wrong with this place?
- They don't evaluate the clientele.
- I thought we just weren't cool enough.
- 他们不评价的客户。
- 我以为我们只是没有足够的冷静。
你是一个美丽的人。知道什么
当我们得到我们的俱乐部我们该怎么办？
You are a beautiful man. Know what
we're gonna do when we get our club?
我们要对待所有的崇拜者只是
以及任何传奇的电视明星。
We're gonna treat all wannabes just
as well as any legendary tv-star.
- That's pretty Roosevelt of you.
- It's just what I believe in.
- 这就是你漂亮罗斯福。
- 这正是我相信英寸
- Wanna dance?
- We're not in the club yet.
- 想跳舞？
- 我们不是在俱乐部呢。
So, maybe when we get in?
所以，也许，当我们进去呢？
So I'm waiting to use the pay phone,
and this guy tips his hat like this.
所以我等待使用公用电话，
这家伙提示他的帽子是这样的。
- 又是谁，你认为那个家伙是？
- 埃米利奥埃斯特韦斯！
- And who do you think that guy was?
- Emilio Estevez!
“全能的鸭子”，男人。我发誓
神。我当时一样，“埃米利奥！”
'The Mighty Duck', man. I swear
to God. I was, like, "Emilio!"
“埃米利奥..！”
"Emilio..!"
The club is closed, folks. Sorry.
该俱乐部是封闭的，伙计。抱歉。
- Nozzled你，我的朋友。
- 完全让我。
- Nozzled you, my friend.
- Totally got me.
那是在我的鼻子。
That was in my nose.
- 你是个白痴。
- 哦，是吗？你喜欢它。
- You're an idiot.
- Oh yeah? You like it.
Get off... Watch it!
下车......当心！
Where's Mom? And who's this
gorgeous young hottie in the kitchen?
哪里的妈妈？而谁是这个
华丽的年轻辣妹在厨房里？
- Why is she wearing Mom's bathrobe?
- What do you think of my new chin?
- 为什么她穿着妈妈的浴袍？
- 你觉得我的新下巴？
ls it better than last year's?
LS比去年的更好？
Behave yourselves. Look who's
gracing us with their presence.
表现自己。看看谁
杀入我们与他们的存在。
- 谁？
- 在这里，爸爸。
- Who?
- Here, Dad.
这是一个健康的震动。
LT帮我打我的身体峰值。
It's a health shake.
lt helps me hit my physical peak.
拿相机。
他会打他的巅峰。
Get the camera.
He's gonna hit his peak.
- Honey, do it in your room.
- Oh, Mom, you're so funny.
- 亲爱的，做在你的房间。
- 哦，妈妈，你太逗了。
Steve? In the store in a haIf hour.
Wear something nice. Emily's back.
史蒂夫？在店里的haIf小时。
穿一件好事。艾米莉的背部。
As if he gives a flying rat's ass.
仿佛他给出了一个飞鼠的屁股。
"Flying rat's ass..."
That would be wild to see.
“飞天老鼠的屁股......”
这将是野看到的。
史蒂夫，在商店中haIf小时。
带上你跳舞的猴子兄弟。
Steve, at the store in a haIf hour.
Bring your dancing monkey brother.
喂，你是从外地来的？
你有一个本地号码？
Hey, are you from out of town?
You have a local number?
Are you all right? Sure?
你没事吧？确定吗？
Finally. An hour and a haIf late.
Steve, go dust the roses.
终于。一个小时haIf晚。
史蒂夫，去尘的玫瑰。
ldiot男孩，
去覆盖收银。
ldiot boy,
go cover the cash register.
ldiot男孩，
去覆盖收银。
Hi. How are you paying for these?
Cash, check or charge?
你好。你是如何支付这些？
现金，支票还是信用卡？
- Charge.
- Okay.
- 充电。
- 好吧。
- ls this a Visa or a Mastercard?
- Move your thumb.
- LS这个Visa或万事达？
- 将你的拇指。
很好的一个。好吧。
Good one. Okay.
确定这是你的卡？这不是
处理。我要调用它。
Sure this is your card? It's not
processing. I have to call it in.
- Operator 238, please.
- Authorisation. Card number?
- 操作员238，请。
- 授权。卡号？
- What's up?
- I told you not to call anymore.
- 这是怎么回事？
- 我告诉过你不要来找我了。
- I need an approval.
- Card number?
- 我需要一个审批。
- 卡号？
- Not the card, sweetness, me.
- Shut up and swipe it.
- 不卡，甜度，我。
- 闭嘴，刷卡吧。
我可以去试试。
I can go for that.
你喜欢吗？这是否感觉很好吗？
因为我可以整夜刷卡吧。
You like that? Does that feel good?
'Cause I can swipe it all night.
- 该卡的罚款。再见，道格。
- 再见，238。
- The card's fine. Bye, Doug.
- Bye, 238.
你好。我可以帮你吗？
Hi. Can I help you?
嗨，道格。您的夜总会太酷了。
我的模型的朋友可以进来吗？
Hi, Doug. Your nightclub's so cool.
Can my model friends come in?
- No. Yes.
- You're so funny and cute and tall.
- 否是。
- 你是那么有趣和可爱和高大。
Let's shake it.
让我们动摇它。
What are you doing? You have to cut up
my plants and make toys of them?
你在做什么？你不得不削减了
我的工厂，使他们的玩具？
- It's a club with a jungle theme.
- You're a jungle theme.
- 这是一个丛林主题的俱乐部。
- 你是个丛林主题。
Go find your brother and load
the trucks. ldiot... Useless!
去找你的兄弟和负载
卡车。 ldiot ......没用！
- Steve..?
- Don't look.
- 史蒂夫..？
- 不要看。
- 嗨，史蒂夫。嘿，道格。
- 不管。
- Hi, Steve. Hey, Doug.
- Whatever.
Now I'm back,
so we can get together.
现在，我回来了，
所以我们可以走到一起。
- You wanna go see a movie?
- Sure.
- 你想去看电影吗？
- 当然。
Or we could just drive around
and make out. I love making out.
或者我们可以只是带动周边
而做出来的。我爱拍出来。
- And I'm really good at it.
- Sounds good.
- 我真的很擅长。
- 听起来不错。
背过，Chicklett。我和哥哥
我，我们住的生活的快车道。
Back off, Chicklett. My brother and
I, we live life in the fast lane.
That means no stop signs,
no pulling over to take pictures.
这意味着没有停止的迹象，
没有拉过来拍照。
See this man? He's my co-pilot
on this magic carpet ride.
看到这个人吗？他是我的副驾驶
在此乘坐魔毯。
- 你只是太多的行李。
- 闭嘴，道格。
- You're just way too much luggage.
- Shut up, Doug.
Emily?
I see you've picked the right son.
艾米丽？
我看你已经选对了儿子。
You know, Steve likes you very much.
你知道，史蒂夫很喜欢你。
Butabi先生。 LS史蒂夫询问艾米丽
再嫁给他吗？
Mr. Butabi. ls Steve asking Emily
to marry him again?
你知道吗？
如果他们有足够的孩子， -
You know something?
If they have enough children, -
- 我们不会有雇用推销员。
we won't have to hire salesmen.
- 哦，Kamehl，你杀了我。
- 不，你杀了我，桑德森先生。
- Oh, Kamehl, you kill me.
- No, you kill me, Mr. Sanderson.
- Can you please leave Steve alone?
- He likes the girl... Yes, you do!
- 可以请你离开史蒂夫一个人吗？
- 他喜欢的女孩......是的，你这样做！
你看这墙呢？之后，他们
结婚后，我们将结合门店 -
You see this wall? After they
get married, we'll combine stores -
- and have the first plant-lamp
shop. Steve and Emily will run it.
- 并具有第一家工厂灯
店。史蒂夫和艾米丽将运行它。
- Maybe you can clean the toilets.
- You're living on "Fantasy lsland".
- God, that was a sweet show.
- I have a fantasy.
That I have two capable sons.
Not one with his head up his ass!
ls this how you load trucks?
Disgusting. Get out of here.
LS这个你怎么加载卡车？
恶心。离开这里。
- 所以，我们是在休息？
- 我猜。
- So we're on a break?
- I guess.
- 你想紧缩呢？
- 当然。让我们来紧缩。
- You wanna crunch it?
- Sure. Let's crunch.
- Can the rest of us use the mirror?
- Appreciate it.
- 我们其他人可以使用镜子？
- 欣赏它。
- Everyone's got an attitude here.
- Gentlemen! Looking large.
- 每个人的在这里得到了一个态度。
- 先生们！寻找大。
Want my power bar?
How about an energy bar?
希望我的力量吧？
怎么样的能量棒？
- I got a muscle triplicator bar.
- Supplements aside...
- 我有一个肌肉triplicator吧。
- 补充抛开...
- How long have we been friends?
- All seven years of high school.
- 多长时间了，我们一直是朋友？
- 所有七岁月高中。
这就是为什么我不会粉饰
它。我很担心你的三头肌。
That's why I'm not gonna sugar coat
it. I'm worried about your triceps.
你不会一路下跌。
我没有看到完全伸直。
You aren't going all the way down.
I'm not seeing full extension.
我们有关于长谈
那天晚上。
We had a long talk about that
the other night.
You just shouldn't cheat yourselves.
Sorry to come down on you like this.
你刚才不应该欺骗自己。
对不起下来就你这个样子。
That's why we love you and hate you.
这就是为什么我们爱你，恨你。
- Still friends?
- You know it.
- 还是朋友吗？
- 你知道它。
I'm glad we had this talk.
我很高兴我们有这样的谈话。
我的店里一个伟大的想法...
I had a great idea for the store...
这家店？你应该是
想着......嘿，这是怎么回事？
The store? You're supposed to be
thinking about... Hey, what's up?
- Can we call you sometime?
- Want some of this?
- 我们可以打电话给你？
- 想要一些这方面？
- Think about our future.
- You're Mount St. Helensing on me.
- 想想我们的未来。
- 你是摩圣Helensing我。
Why are you forgetting our plans?
为什么你忘记了我们的计划？
The plans about you and I opening up
only the coolest club a la the Roxbury.
你和我开拓计划
只有最酷的俱乐部一拉罗克斯伯里。
- How? We can't even get in.
- We're letting them not let us in.
- 怎么了？我们甚至不能进入。
- 我们让他们不会让我们进去。
But no more. It's time we step up
into that sweet-ass world.
但没有更多。这时候，我们加强
成甜美的屁股世界。
从现在开始，唯一的俱乐部
我们要的是罗克斯伯里。
From now on, the only club
we're going to is the Roxbury.
- 我们不能...
- 我们能。你知道为什么吗？
- We can't...
- We can. You know why?
- 我们好找？
- 非常好看。你特别。
- We're good looking?
- Very good looking. You especially.
跟着我念：
我们可以进入罗克斯伯里。
Repeat after me:
We can get into the Roxbury.
我们可以进入罗克斯伯里。
Roxbury..!
罗克斯伯里..！
Hey, what's up? You want some
of this? How about a little of that?
嘿，这是怎么回事？你想要一些
这个？如何一点点呢？
She starts to smell them.
She thought they were real plants!
她开始闻到它们。
她以为他们是真正的植物！
- 喂？
- 这是怎么回事？
- Hello?
- What's up?
该Sandersons在这里看到
你母亲的新下巴。穿好衣服。
The Sandersons are here to see
your mother's new chin. Get dressed.
- Sorry, we're a bit busy tonight.
- Steve? I'll be right back.
- 对不起，我们有点忙，今晚。
- 史蒂夫？我马上就回来。
I like your bathing suit. You have
really good muscle definition.
我喜欢你的泳衣。你有
真的好肌肉的定义。
Most Americans don't wear revealing
bathing suits. Very European of you.
大多数美国人不穿暴露
泳衣。很欧洲的你。
It's really sexy and I have
a really good taste in what's sexy.
这真的很性感，我有
一个真正的好味道什么是性感。
- Steve!
- Whatever, Emily.
- 史蒂夫！
- 无论如何，艾米丽。
Good.
好。
这是怎么回事..？
What's going on..?
你是从外地来的..？
Are you from out of town..?
当我告诉你做一些事情，
我的意思是。从来没有进来半裸。
When I tell you to do something,
I mean it. Never come in half-naked.
- Put some clothes on and come down.
- lsn't on our things-to-do-list.
- 把一些衣服和回落。
- lsn't我们的东西，待办事项清单上。
- We have something to do tonight.
- Yes. To get downstairs.
- 我们今晚的东西做。
- 是的。要下楼。
I don't want to!
我不想！
How do I get through
to this individual?
我如何打通
这个人吗？
Doug is like a fax machine.
道格就像是一台传真机。
Without a cover page, people don't
know where it's coming from.
没有封面，让人不
知道它的来源。
有时你听到忙音。
这就是为什么你有一个重拨键。
And sometimes you get a busy signal.
That's why you got a redial button.
- 其实，我总是把事情搞砸...
- 请勿打扰。他永远也不会明白。
- Actually, I always screw it up...
- Don't bother. He'll never understand.
I understand very well. You're going
to a new, hot club tonight, right?
我非常理解。你要去
到一个新的，热的俱乐部今晚，对不对？
- But how are you gonna get there?
- What are you doing?
- 但是，你要怎么到达那里？
- 你在做什么？
You can take away our phones
and our keys, but not our dreams.
你可以拿走我们的手机
和我们的钥匙，但不是我们的梦想。
'Cos we're, like, sleeping
when we have them.
因为此刻我们一样，睡觉
当我们有他们。
Later much!
以后多！
Boys, wait. I don't like you leaving
without a phone.
男孩，等待。我不喜欢你离开
没有一个电话。
How old are these? How embarrassing.
你几岁了这些？多么尴尬。
You know, in case of emergency.
Have fun.
要知道，在紧急情况下。
有乐趣。
- 难道让妈妈的口红在我身上？
- LT看起来像你亲热。
- Did Mom get lipstick on me?
- lt looks like you were making out.
- How's my hair? Roxbury-good?
- You know it.
- 如何是我的头发吗？ Roxbury的，好不好？
- 你知道它。
I've got to tell you, Steve,
tonight, I can taste it.
我得告诉你，史蒂夫，
今晚，我可以品尝它。
我不能品尝它。我很害怕现在。
我不知道该怎么办。
I can't taste it. I'm so scared right now.
I don't know what to do.
- You're mad-cowing on me. Relax.
- I'm nervous.
- 正是这种压力进入。
- 你必须把自己的控制权。
- It's this pressure to get in.
- You must take control of yourself.
No, you take control.
I'm barely hanging on here.
不，你掌握控制权。
我勉强挂在这里。
来吧，放松身心。觉得小狗
和糖果手杖，好吗？
Come on, relax. Think puppies
and candy canes, all right?
- Hey, hotlegs. What's going on?
- We'll clean it up later. Don't worry.
- 嘿，hotlegs。这是怎么回事？
- 我们将在后面清理。不要担心。
I see your Roxbury balloon
and I hate to burst it, -
我看到你的气球罗克斯伯里
我恨用来破灭的吧， -
- 但我不认为
我们的名字都在此列。
- but I don't think
our names are on that list.
Perfect. "Rites of Passage".
完美的。 “礼记通道”。
Remember? A boy in the jungle
with only a spear to hunt the lion.
还记得吗？在丛林的男孩
只用矛捕猎狮子。
这款车是我们的矛。
这Roxbury的是我们的狮子。
This van is our spear.
That Roxbury is our lion.
- 是否保镖知道吗？
- 他是要找出答案。
- Does the bouncer know about this?
- He's about to find out.
下周见。
See you next week.
- My good hombre. Remember us?
- Doug and Steve Butabi.
- 我的好HOMBRE。还记得我们吗？
- 道格和史蒂夫Butabi。
- You're brothers?
- No... Yes.
- 你是兄弟？
- 不......是的。
- Man!
- Works every time.
- 人！
- 屡试不爽。
Now I remember. You can't come in.
现在我还记得。你不能进来。
What's up, partner?
How are you doing tonight?
这是怎么回事，合作伙伴？
如何你今天晚上干什么？
时间玩一个小垒球。
Time to play a little softball.
- 嘿，好男人。怎么样了？
- 良好。你stilI不能进来。
- Hey, good man. How's it going?
- Good. You stilI can't come in.
That's not what my friend told me.
His name is Abraham.
这不是我的朋友告诉我的。
他的名字叫亚伯拉罕。
- You don't know him?
- What about his two friends?
- 你不认识他吗？
- 那么他的两个朋友？
George Washington
and George Washington?
乔治·华盛顿
和乔治·华盛顿？
And George Washington is a little
lonely. Wants to join his buddies.
和乔治·华盛顿是一个小
孤独。想要加入他的哥们。
And look who else we've got.
Roosevelt, Roosevelt and Jefferson.
再看看还有谁，我们已经有了。
罗斯福，罗斯福和杰弗逊。
谢谢...大。
Thanks... Great.
- ls that an ATM?
- That's where we drop off videos.
- LS，一个自动取款机？
- 这就是我们下车的视频。
- Hello, that's it.
- That was a card store.
- 你好，仅此而已。
- 这是一个卡存储。
- That's just Weight Watchers...
- ATM. That's it.
- 这只是慧俪轻体...
- 自动取款机。就是这样。
- Shit. The car.
- What about me?
- 妈的。这款车。
- 那我呢？
This racing car is illegal.
All I need is a police report.
该赛车是非法的。
所有我需要的是一个警察报告。
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, let me see.
- 你没事吧？
- 是啊，让我看看。
Great. They're starting
with the neck injuries. I'm screwed.
大。他们开始
与颈部受伤。我搞砸了。
Jesus, man.
耶稣的人。
- 对不起你的面包车。
- 没办法。理查德GRIECO！
- Sorry about your van.
- No way. Richard Grieco!
- 我们看到你在罗克斯伯里。
- 右。那你想干什么？
- We saw you at the Roxbury.
- Right. So what do you want to do?
- Go to the Roxbury again.
- We couldn't get in.
- 转到罗克斯伯里一次。
- 我们进不去。
You want me to get you
into the Roxbury? Great. Follow me.
你要我给你
进入罗克斯伯里？大。跟我来。
- Amazing.
- lt all comes from within.
- 惊人的。
- LT全部来自内心。
他觉得这是因为他是一个演员。
He felt it because he's an actor.
我们得让停在罗克斯伯里。
我只是不想打官司。
We gotta make a stop at the Roxbury.
I just don't want a lawsuit.
哦，我的上帝，这是最
令人惊叹的地方我去过。
Oh, my God, this is the most
amazing place I've ever been.
This is the coatroom.
The club's in there.
这是衣帽间。
该俱乐部是在那里。
What's up..?
这是怎么回事..？
- 获取控制住自己。
- 这是在这里棘手超载。
- Get a hold of yourself.
- It's hottie overload in here.
- 只是自己的步伐。
- 这是怎么回事？二，三，四。
- Just pace yourself.
- What's up? Two, three, four.
What's up? Two, three, four...
这是怎么回事？二，三，四......
- Sweet!
- 甜！
Richie, good to see you. Get over here.
里奇，很高兴见到你。在这里渡过。
- 这个地方被踢。
- 跳跃像“21跳街”。
- The place is kicking.
- Jumping like "21 Jump Street".
Who are your friends?
谁是你的朋友？
- The owner.
- The man we want to be.
- 雇主。
- 我们想成为的人。
- 我以为我们想成为GRIECO。
- 专业，这是这个家伙。
- I thought we wanted to be Grieco.
- Professionally, it's this guy.
Dooey，我的主要人。我喜欢
这名男子。满足Butabi兄弟。
Dooey, my main man. I love
this man. Meet the Butabi brothers.
These are good boys.
Did you grab my ass?
这些都是很好的男生。
你抢了我的屁股？
- No, sir. I did not grab your ass.
- It's okay if you did.
- 不，先生。我没有抢你的屁股。
- 没关系，如果你没有。
I understand. It's just that
you're barking up the wrong tree.
我明白了。这只是
你找错了树。
- You guys come here a lot?
- All the time.
- 你们到这里来了很多？
- 所有的时间。
- But we've never been inside.
- Watch what you're saying.
- 但是，我们从来没有进去过。
- 注意你在说什么。
So, is Johnny Depp meeting you here?
那么，是约翰尼·德普在这儿见到你？
号
No.
好吧......听着，本尼，
回头见。见你，伙计们。
All right... Listen, Bennie,
see you later. See you, guys.
- See you, Richard Grieco.
- See you, Grieco's lady.
- 见你，理查德GRIECO。
- 再见，GRIECO的淑女。
I'm honoured to shoot the shit with
the owner of the club of all clubs.
我很荣幸拍摄的狗屎
所有俱乐部的会所的所有者。
- And we're proficient club hoppers.
- We usually go to the Mudd Club.
- 我们是精通俱乐部料斗。
- 我们通常去的穆德俱乐部。
- That place is rank.
- They let any asswad in the door.
- 那个地方是军衔。
- 他们让在门的任何asswad。
- 我自己的那个地方也。
- 这是一个非常好的位置，但。
- I own that place also.
- It's a really good location, though.
不，你说得对。一天
你热，第二天你不是。
No, you're right. One day
you're hot, the next day you're not.
其实，我有一个想法的俱乐部。
Actually, I had an idea for a club.
- Wait. Did you grab my ass?
- No.
- 等待。你抢了我的屁股？
- 号
- Do you want to?
- No. Should I?
- 你想？
- 号要这样呢？
Okay. Continue.
好吧。继续。
People waiting outside are bummed,
'cos they're trying to get in.
人在外面等着被摄影课，
'因为他们正试图进入。
What if the outside of the club
looked like the inside?
如果有什么俱乐部的外
看上去像里面？
带沙发和音乐和所有。
但随后在里面......
With couches and music and all that.
But then on the inside...
......它看起来像街头。
要知道，汽车和体征。
... it looks like the street.
You know, cars and signs.
外侧是内侧
和内侧的外侧。
The outside is the inside
and the inside is the outside.
不吹你的心？
Doesn't that blow your mind?
- 怎么样的人？
- 拥有一间餐厅。之一。
- What about that guy?
- Owns a restaurant. One.
- Boy, has this place gone downhill.
- No one over six figures. Let's go.
- 男孩，已经这个地方走了下坡路。
- 没有人超过六位数。让我们去。
- Wait. That's that Zadir guy.
- Who are those guys with him?
- 等待。就是这样Zadir家伙。
- 谁是那些家伙和他在一起？
If they're with Zadir,
they've got to be worth something.
如果他们与Zadir，
他们必须是值得的东西。
Great. Let's work.
大。让我们携手。
- 告诉他关于吸血鬼的想法。
- 这是一个愚蠢的想法。
- Tell him about the vampire idea.
- That's a dumb idea.
我必须打个招呼金凯瑞。
I have to say hello to Jim Carrey.
来到这里，
你的宠物侦探混蛋。
Come here,
you pet detective bastard.
“吸烟”，你疯了狗娘养的。
"Smoking", you crazy son of a bitch.
- 是我太爱出风头？难道我说话呢？
- 你是完全阐明。
- Was I too pushy? Did I speak well?
- You were totally articulate.
It's hard to pitch in a nightclub.
The music is way too loud in here.
很难在一家夜总会在球场。
音乐是太大声在这里。
We have to get a meeting. Steve..?
我们必须得到一个会议。史蒂夫..？
- You want to dance?
- Yes.
- 你想跳舞吗？
- 是的。
- All right. Take it easy.
- She said yes.
- 好吧。别紧张。
- 她说是的。
Hotties wanna shake it. Come on.
帅哥美女想动摇它。来吧。
这是一些很好的屁股，霎那
对那里发生的。
That's some good ass-grabbing
going on there.
1 980。不错的一年。
1980. Good year.
Excellent year. Devo had a huge hit.
出色的一年。泥盆有一个巨大的打击。
- 与“琼妮爱插翅”开始。
- 插翅给出了一个关于琼妮他妈的。
- And "Joanie Loves Chachi" started.
- Chachi gives a fuck about Joanie.
Cambi makes a good point.
But tonight we have some fun.
汇兑银行做一个好点的。
但今晚我们有一些乐趣。
- Sweet suds, Mr. Zadir.
- But you know what makes a party?
- 甜沫，Zadir先生。
- 但是，你知道是什么让一个政党？
- Fluffy whip.
- But not putting it on stuff.
- 蓬松鞭。
- 但不是把它放在东西。
You press the little white nozzle
and you suck on it. It's fun.
按下白色的小喷嘴
你吸就可以了。它的乐趣。
- You mean, like, nitrous oxide?
- No. What is that?
- 你的意思是，像，一氧化二氮？
- 号是什么？
Dooey，我们要停下来，找
有些蓬松鞭党。
Dooey, we have to stop and get
some fluffy whip for the party.
- 是的，先生。
- LT必须处于一个即可。
- Yes, sir.
- lt has to be in a can.
他不能听到您的声音。
He can't hear you.
嘿，Dooey，告诉你妈妈
我有一个很好的时间昨晚。
Hey, Dooey, tell your mom
I had a nice time last night.
- And your dad.
- What?
- 和你的爸爸。
- 什么？
- I mean, your sister.
- Good one!
- 我的意思是，你的妹妹。
- 好一个！
- Only in a Limo.
- We nailed him.
- 只有在豪华轿车。
- 我们钉了他。
Disco-dicks.
迪斯科 - 迪克斯。
- And that alien was Robin Williams.
- I'll be right back.
- 这是外星人罗宾·威廉斯。
- 我马上就回来。
- It's my boss's card.
- I'll take care of that.
- 这是我老板的卡。
- 我会采取照顾。
- 操作员238，请。
- 你好，道格。
- Operator 238, please.
- Hello, Doug.
- 猜猜我们今晚去了。
- 上拉的一站式市场？
- Guess where we went tonight.
- The One-Stop Market on Ventura?
没有，我之前的意思是，
你狡猾，一点信用狐狸精。
No, I mean before that,
you sly, little credit vixen.
I give up, you nasty card-swiper.
我放弃了，你讨厌的卡刷卡。
- The Roxbury. Come out some time.
- I would.
- 罗克斯伯里。出来一段时间了。
- 我会的。
But then who would approve
all the money you spend?
但是谁也批准
所有的钱你花？
- You're always thinking of me.
- The card's good. Bye, Doug.
- 你总是想着我。
- 该卡的不错。再见，道格。
She approved. Approved.
她批准。批准。
- 甜蜜的屁股住宅，Zadir先生。
- 这是一个地方挂我的帽子。
- Sweet-ass dwelling, Mr. Zadir.
- It's a place to hang my hat.
Look. A hundred thousand dollar
sound system, and nobody's dancing.
看。一十万美元
音响系统，和任何人的舞蹈。
If I may congest, the pool is taking
up the prime dancing real estate.
如果我可以充血，池正在
了首要的舞蹈房地产。
If you put glass over the pool,
it would be like dancing on water.
如果你把玻璃在池，
它会像跳舞的水。
- And people love to do that.
- Let's not talk business now.
- 而人们喜欢这样做。
- 让我们不要谈业务了。
让我们来建立一个会议。
Let's set up a meeting.
安娜·妮可？装上去的。
你让我们生病。
Anna Nicole? Put something on.
You're making us sick.
会议！
Meeting!
- Let's mingle.
- Right.
- 让我们打成一片。
- 右。
This ltalian food tastes so good.
It's, like, Mexican.
这的义大利菜的口味这么好。
它的一样，墨西哥。
- Could you pass me a towel, please?
- Good. How are you?
- 你能递给我一条毛巾，好吗？
- 良好。你怎么样？
- They're right behind you.
- BMW... Vanilla, mostly.
- 他们是在你身后。
- 宝马...香草，大多。
- There you are.
- We got scared.
- 你来了。
- 我们害怕了。
- Of who? We'll kick his ass.
- No.
- 是谁？我们会踢他的屁股。
- 号
We got scared
somebody stole you away from us.
我们吓坏了
有人偷了你离我们远去。
Oh, okay.
哦，好吧。
像其他一些女生
会偷我们而去......
Like some other girls
would steal us away...
哦，对了。哦！
Oh, right. Oh!
所以，做你们想去某个地方
我们单独相处的？
So, do you guys wanna go some place
we can be alone?
No... Yes! Oh, man.
不......是的！哦，伙计。
- Why does it taste so sweet?
- 'Cos it's like candy.
- 为什么它的味道这么甜？
- 因为这一切就像糖果。
These are real.
They'll be dead in a week.
这些都是真实的。
他们会死在一个星期。
You know what I always thought
would make a cool 'Twilight Zone"?
你知道我一直以为
会做一个很酷的“阴阳魔界”？
就像我们看到的图片
这位女士的， -
Like, we see a picture
of this lady, -
- 但这位女士，是我们刚刚
我们的照片吗？想过吗？
- but to this lady, are we just
a picture of us? Ever think of that?
号
No.
你为什么不来这里了？
Why don't you come over here?
薇薇卡，你知道我听到
当我第一次见到你？
Vivica, you know what I heard
when I first met you?
什么？
What?
- What are you doing?
- That's an ambulance.
- 你在做什么？
- 这是一辆救护车。
Coming to take me away.
The sight of you stopped my heart.
来带我走。
看见你停我的心脏。
Cambi, do you like blueberries
or strawberries?
汇兑银行，你喜欢蓝莓
或草莓？
我想知道是什么样的煎饼
命令你在早晨。
I wanna know what kind of pancakes
to order you in the morning.
Steve!
史蒂夫！
- 我不知道...
- 你在做什么？
- I was wondering...
- What are you doing?
检查您的标签。
正如我想。在天上。
Checking your label.
Just as I thought. Made in heaven.
Doug. You've gotten past
the opening lines.
道格。你已经得到了过去
开头几行。
- ls that a mirror in your pocket?
- What?
- LS，在你的口袋里的镜子？
- 什么？
我可以看到myseIf在你的裤子。
I could see myseIf in your pants.
如果我说你有一个好身体，
你会嫌弃我？
If I said you had a nice body,
would you hold it against me?
I was there. I was, like, "Emilio!"
And Doug was going cra...
我在那里。我当时一样，“埃米利奥！”
和Doug要去CRA ...
And Steve was, like, "Emilio!"
Oh, God, if you were only there.
和史蒂夫是一样，“埃米利奥！”
哦，上帝，如果你只在那里。
我觉得自己是一个自私的猪，怎么回事
关于我自己。你怎么样？
I feel like a selfish pig, going on
about myself. What about you?
你是哪里人？
有兄弟姐妹吗？任何家庭？
Where are you from?
Any brothers or sisters? Any family?
- Pets, what about pets?
- I got a cat.
- 宠物，怎么样的宠物？
- 我有一只猫。
Really? A cat? lnteresting.
真的吗？猫？ lnteresting。
我觉得你更象是一个爱狗之人。
也许一个博美犬。拉萨犬。
I think of you more as a dog person.
Maybe a Pomeranian. Lhasa Apso.
东西不多，温暖，模糊...
Something small, warm, fuzzy...
LS这是你第一次？
ls this your first time?
Yes. lsn't it yours?
是。 lsn't你的吗？
- ls this your first time?
- What?
- LS这是你第一次？
- 什么？
Are you serious?
Oh, you're hilarious.
你是认真的？
呵呵，你很搞笑。
Oh, man. You're funny.
Hey, Steve? You're a funny girl.
哦，伙计。你很有趣。
嘿，史蒂夫？你是个有趣的女孩。
All right. Hey, where are you going?
好的。嘿，你要去哪里？
- Oh, my God.
- Did you just? 'Cos I just...
- 噢，我的上帝。
- 只要是吗？ “因为我只是...
Not that it hasn't happened before.
lt was okay.
不，它没有发生过。
LT还行。
I'm gonna go back in and...
我会在回去...
- Hey, Steve?
- Yeah, Doug?
- 嘿，史蒂夫？
- 是啊，道格？
- You got a number.
- We got a number.
- 你有一个数字。
- 我们得到了一个号码。
我得到了一些伟大的办公用品
我们的新的夜总会业务。
I got some great office supplies
for our new nightclub business.
后LT笔记注释重要
文档。
Post-lt notes to annotate important
documents.
Little ones. You write smaller than
me. Mugs with our names on them.
小家伙们。你写的小于
我。马克杯与我们对他们的名字。
Yours say Doug.
Did you call Mr. Zadir?
你说的道格。
你叫Zadir先生？
Before you talk to a man like Mr. Zadir,
you have to have a plan of attack.
之前你跟喜欢Zadir先生一个人，
你必须有一个行动的计划。
I'd like to schedule a meeting.
Can you do... 12:30?
我想安排会议。
你可以做... 1 2:30？
Let me see.
让我看看。
- 我很清楚。
- 你知道吗？
- I'm clear.
- You know what?
让我们有一个预先的会议
我们的会议之前进行头脑风暴。
Let's have a pre-meeting
to brainstorm before our meeting.
Yeah, that way we don't
look like idiots at our meeting.
是啊，这样我们不
看起来像白痴在我们的会议。
- 对不起。注册的封闭。
- 对不起。
- I'm sorry. Register's closed.
- Sorry.
Mr. Butabi,
where's the other cash register?
Butabi先生，
哪来的其他收银？
Steve? I was just thinking. Dad
would be really proud of us right now.
史蒂夫？我只是在想。爸
将是非常自豪我们的现在。
What are you idiots doing? I pay you
to take money and push a button.
什么是你白痴在干什么？我付你
拿钱，并按下一个按钮。
Are your delicate fingers injured?
是你纤细的手指受伤了吗？
- We're working our asses off.
- Our weeks filling up quick.
- 我们正在我们的驴了。
- 我们的星期填满快。
We've made
important business contacts.
我们已经取得了
重要的业务联系。
Dancing the Macarena
with Donald Trump?
跳舞的Macarena
与唐纳德特朗普？
You're always telling us
to do something with our lives.
你总是告诉我们
做一些与我们的生活。
You never support us or care about
what's important to us, right?
你永远支持我们或关心
什么是重要的我们，对不对？
- Yeah... for the most part.
- Even your brother isn't convinced.
- 是啊......大部分。
- 即使你弟弟不服气。
Why? He uses his brain, unlike you.
You're a loser! New policy.
为什么呢？他用他的大脑，不像你。
你是个失败者！新政策。
没有更多的俱乐部。
没错！你的生活是零售。
No more clubs.
Yes! Your life is retail.
- Go clean the stockroom.
- You know what?
- 去清理库房。
- 你知道吗？
Not only will we not clean out
the stockroom, we're out of here!
我们不仅不清理掉
库房，我们离开这里吧！
怎么样的库房？
What about the stockroom?
We don't need you.
We made huge-ass contacts last night.
我们不需要你。
我们取得了巨大的屁股接触昨晚。
再加上我们遇到这些女孩，爸爸。
Plus we met these girls, Dad.
We'll make it without you.
You'lI see.
我们将使它没有你。
You'lI见。
I'lI see when you come home, begging
for food and shelter. Morons!
当你回家I'lI看到，乞讨
对食物和住所。白痴！
Steve? You're an ass, Doug.
You want to go to the beach later?
史蒂夫？你是驴，道格。
你想要去海边以后呢？
I know a beach where you don't have
to wear a bathing suit.
我知道一个海滩，在那里你没有
穿泳衣。
- Plus with my milky white skin...
- This is a major family crisis.
- 加上我的乳白色的皮肤...
- 这是一个重大的家庭危机。
只要给我打个电话，如果你想
出门。或者只是叫我反正。
Just give me a call if you wanna
go out. Or just call me anyway.
You notice we forgot to ask her
something. That's weird.
您会注意到，我们忘了问她
东西。这是奇怪的。
We're in serious relationships right
now, and our ladies can trust us.
我们在认真的关系正确
现在，我们的女士们可以信任我们。
Why go out for burgers,
when you got steak at home?
为什么出去的汉堡，
当你在家里有牛排吗？
- 你没事吧？
- 是啊，挺好的。
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, fine.
- 道格和史蒂夫Butabi。
- 你是兄弟？
- Doug and Steve Butabi.
- You're brothers?
- 我们都进不了的现在。
- 你的名字不在名单上。
- We can't get into that right now.
- Your names are not on the list.
We have a meeting.
我们有一个会议。
- Doug, Mr. Zadir!
- Security.
- 道格，Zadir先生！
- 安全性。
- Dooey... Yeah. Up top.
- Main man.
- Dooey ...是啊。往上顶。
- 主的人。
- Raging party last night.
- ls that what my mother told you?
- 愤怒的党昨晚。
- LS是我妈妈告诉你的？
- 什么？
- 蓬松的鞭子是一个很大的打击。
- What?
- The fluffy whip was a big hit.
- 我被派去寻找更多。
- 你，先生，是一个派对动物。
- I was sent out looking for more.
- You, sir, are a party animal.
It's been great spending quality
time, but we're meeting Mr. Zadir.
这是伟大的消费质量
时间，但我们要去见Zadir先生。
Zadir was drunk last night.
He doesn't even remember you.
Zadir喝醉了昨晚。
他甚至不记得你。
你以为你是第一个失败者
我已经在周一摆脱？
You think you're the first losers
I've had to get rid of on a Monday?
- Are we being blown off?
- Actually, you're being kicked out.
- 难道我们被吹走？
- 其实，你被踢出。
That doesn't feel good at all...
那感觉并不好所有...
- What's going on?
- Just some trespassers.
- 这是怎么回事？
- 只是一些入侵者。
- And the boys from last night?
- I haven't located them yet.
- 而从昨晚的男生？
- 我已经不在他们呢。
Dooey，你刚才抢了我的屁股？
Dooey, did you just grab my ass?
从我站在那里，
这是一个物理上是不可能。
From where I'm standing,
that's a physical impossibility.
I know your tricks, Dooey.
我知道你的把戏，Dooey。
Maybe we should just go back to work.
也许我们应该回去上班。
Maybe we should go to college, not
put gel in our hair and wear jeans!
也许我们应该去上大学，不
把凝胶在我们的头发和穿牛仔裤！
- 让我们做的是，史蒂夫！
- 对不起。
- Let's do that, Steve!
- Sorry.
Cambi's number.
汇兑银行的数量。
- We had a pretty sweet time, right?
- Sweet-ass time.
- 我们有一个非常甜蜜的时间，对不对？
- 甜蜜的屁股时间。
So you do travel to places
other than Japan.
所以，你做旅游的地方
日本以外。
- 这些火辣是甜的。
- 甜蜜的屁股甜蜜。
- These hotties are sweet.
- Sweet ass sweet.
- Who is it?
- Just a bunch of pound signs.
- 你是谁？
- 只是一堆井号。
- 你做得对吗？
- 你必须打的井号。
- Are you doing it right?
- You have to hit the pound sign.
You have to put in our number
and then hit the pound sign.
你必须把我们的数
然后打的井号。
Excuse me, Bill Nye, the science guy.
对不起，比尔·奈伊，科学的家伙。
这是一个甜蜜的表演，太。
That's a sweet show, too.
Cambi, it's your boyfriend.
Look, I need to see you.
汇兑银行，这是你的男朋友。
你看，我要见你。
- I'm at the Skybar.
- We'll be rig there.
- 我在Skybar酒吧。
- 我们将钻机在那里。
- Nice.
- I was focused the whole time.
- 尼斯。
- 我是专注的全部时间。
你有一个很好的时间上晚？
Did you have a good time last night?
我有一个伟大的时间。
我认为我们已经达到了一个点 -
I had a great time.
I think we've reached a point -
- 在那里我可以叫你口水巾
并留下了“ICA”。
- where I can call you Viv
and leave out the "ica".
你想挂出
或做什么，我们昨天晚上做了？
You wanna hang out
or do what we did last night?
- Or eat, then do what we did?
- Sounds good.
- 或吃，然后做我们所做的？
- 听起来不错。
- Have your boarding passes ready.
- You'lI have to check your bag.
- 让你的登机牌准备好了。
- You'lI要检查你的包。
The movie on this flight will be...
I can't think of any more.
在这次飞行的电影将是...
我想不出任何更多。
- Where's your car?
- Our dad got mad, took it away.
- 哪里是你的车吗？
- 我们的爸爸生气了，把它拿走。
We used to work for him, but we quit
today. Actually, we're unemployed.
我们曾经为他工作，但我们不干
今天。其实，我们是失业。
- 你不Zadir先生工作？
- 我们刚认识他的最后一晚。
- You don't work with Mr. Zadir?
- We just met him last night.
- We will be. So no, but yes.
- If we ever get to see him again.
- 我们将。因此，没有，但肯定的。
- 如果我们曾经得到再次见到他。
- 你不需要登机牌。
- 获取离我们远去。
- You don't need boarding passes.
- Get away from us.
- You guys are a big waste of time.
- Como what?
- 你们是时间的巨大浪费。
- 科莫什么？
- Steve, you're a jerkoff.
- I'm glad you shared that with me.
- 史蒂夫，你是头晕晕的。
- 我很高兴你分享了我。
- It's a big step for both of us.
- Consider last night a favor.
- 这是我们俩的一大步。
- 考虑昨晚的忙。
Now do us a favor.
Never talk to us again!
现在，帮一下忙。
千万别跟我们了！
- What did we do? We'll change.
- You can't change.
- 我们做了什么？我们会改变。
- 你不能改变的。
You are ugly, pathetic losers.
你是丑陋的，可怜的失败者。
I can't believe we actually had sex
with these asswads!
我简直不敢相信我们居然发生了性关系
这些asswads！
这就是问题所在。笨人不佳
看起来一模一样的笨人丰富。
That's the problem. Poor schmucks
look just the same as rich schmucks.
- No... Yes...
- This is the worst day of my life.
- 不......是的......
- 这是我一生中最糟糕的一天。
I'd really appreciate it
if you didn't talk to me right now.
我会很感激
如果你不跟我说话，现在。
I don't know how to respond to that.
我不知道该如何作出回应。
Big surprise. You don't know how to
work the clubs, talk to the ladies.
大惊喜。你不知道如何
工作的俱乐部，跟我们的女士们。
你只懂得问我
怎么做的一切！
You only know how to ask me
how to do everything!
这就是为什么一切都已经
错了。你抱着我。
That's why everything has gone
wrong. You're holding me back.
你像这个东西绑在我的
腿，在这个链条拖动的事情。
You're like this thing tied to my
leg, this dragging thing on a chain.
- A lead weight?
- Yes, thank you. But not anymore!
- 一个铅块？
- 是的，谢谢你。但现在不是了！
Nothing. That's all. Nothing.
什么都没有。这就是全部。什么都没有。
You can't blame me. Today was just
a series of random events gone awry.
你可别怪我。今天只是
一系列的随机事件出了错。
Maybe they wouldn't go awry
if I had someone next to me with a brain!
也许他们就不会出差错
如果我有一个人在我旁边用脑！
You know what? Dad was right.
You are a loser.
你知道吗？爸爸是对的。
你是一个失败者。
You know what, Steve?
I lied. You're not good looking.
你知道吗，史蒂夫？
我撒了谎。你不是好找。
你说什么？我听不见
事情从低到地面。
Did you say something? I can't hear
things from that low to the ground.
- 我考虑你的前兄弟。
- 我不在乎。
- Consider me your ex-brother.
- I don't care.
Care about this?
You want the real thing?
关心这个？
你想真实的东西？
- Do you want..?
- Stop talking to me.
- 你想..？
- 停止跟我说话。
Fine. My pleasure.
精细。我的荣幸。
Little Post-lts, you little idiot.
小后LTS，你这个小笨蛋。
Get out, 'cos I hate you.
滚出去，“因为我恨你。
- You should take a lesson from it.
- Grieco.
- 你应该汲取教训。
- GRIECO。
- You'll be very happy with these.
- How long do they last?
- 你会很高兴与这些。
- 多久他们持续多久？
They last forever. They're silk.
They'll always be in bloom.
他们永远持续下去。他们是丝绸。
他们会永远盛开。
They'll never die, never change.
Never say you're not good looking.
他们永远不会死，永远不会改变。
永远不要说你不是好找。
They'll always be in your room, not
suddenly move to the guest house.
他们会永远在你的房间，不
突然移动到招待所。
东西已经上来了。对不起。
Something has come up. Excuse me.
- 所有的客户都郁闷。
- 这只是我怀念道格。
- All the customers are depressed.
- It's just that I miss Doug.
- 他在招待所。这是一个豪宅。
- 有没有电缆。
- He's in the guest house. It's a mansion.
- There's no cable.
- Yes, there is. They have Cinemax.
- But there's no HBO. God!
- 是的，有。他们有Cinemax的。
- 但有没有HBO。上帝！
- Feel it right here. Squeeze.
- Hey, Steve.
- 感觉它在这里。挤。
- 嘿，史蒂夫。
I heard about your brother.
我听说你哥哥。
- 所以，当我们要怎么出去？
- 我知道菠菜包裹的地方。
- So when are we gonna go out?
- I know a place with spinach wraps.
I know you've had you heart set on
this, but the truth is, I'm a rebel.
我知道你有你心脏设置
这一点，但事实是，我是一个反叛者。
你是这样的
甜美女孩从隔壁的类型。
You're like this
sweet-girl-from-next-door type.
我去上大学。翻译：醉
狂欢偶尔克里夫笔记。
I go to college. Translation: Drunken
orgies with occasional Cliff notes.
LT听起来不错，但我刚刚出来
这个非常严肃的关系。
lt sounds good, but I just got out
of this very serious relationship.
I have to nurse my emotional wounds.
我要吃奶我的情绪创伤。
That could take till... Saturday.
这可能需要到...星期六。
That's perfect. Your dad got us tickets
for David Copperfield this Saturday.
那很完美。你爸爸把我们的机票
大卫科波菲尔这个星期六。
这会是这么多的乐趣
看东西出现和消失。
It's gonna be so much fun
to see things appear and disappear.
I'lI see you.
I'lI见到你。
- Oh, man. Great glutes.
- I don't care.
- 哦，伙计。大臀部。
- 我不在乎。
- 这是昂贵的。
- 我得走了。
- That's expensive.
- Gotta go.
Who decorates like this?
Steve, come on.
谁装饰这样吗？
史蒂夫，来吧。
“业务。人际关系
在管理“。
"Business. Human Relationships
in Management."
"Covers the development of..."
“涵盖的发展......”
Here's one. "Business Computer
Systems." That's a good one.
这里有一个。 “商务电脑
系统，“这是一个很好的一个。
Machines are Doug's thing.
I'm more of a people person.
机器是道格的事。
我是一个人的人。
A business man must have knowledge
of computers. Come on.
一个商人必须具备的知识
电脑。来吧。
Here's another one.
"Venture Management."
这里是另外一个。
“风险管理”。
Gosh, Emily, school?
I'lI have to read, and homework...
天哪，艾米丽，学校？
I'lI必须阅读和家庭作业...
老师说：“你分享
，与班上其他同学？“
Teachers saying: "Would you share
that with the rest of the class?"
难道你要我少角质？
Do you want me to be less horny?
- 不，这不会是一件好事。
- 看，这就是我们要做的。
- No, that wouldn't be good.
- Look, here's what we do.
首先，我们结合了卖场，好吗？
然后，我们可以添加家具。
First, we combine the stores, okay?
Then we can add the furniture.
Recliners and sofa beds...
躺椅和沙发床...
- And end tables and...
- Chairs.
- 和最终表和...
- 椅子。
- Oh, yes, chairs.
- Ottomans.
- 哦，对了，椅子。
- 脚垫。
Yes, ottomans. We're gonna be bigger
than lkea... Home Depot.
是的，沙发椅。我们要去更大
比lkea ...家得宝。
lkea！
lkea!
I think we're moving way too fast.
You're talking like we're married.
我认为，我们正在移动太快。
你说的一样，我们已经结婚了。
Oh, Steve.
You just made me so happy.
哦，史蒂夫。
你刚才让我太高兴了。
What? No, I don't mean that.
什么？不，我不是那个意思。
It's just that I don't...
只是，我不...
好吧。
Okay.
道格，如果我没有记错的话，
这个地方已经得到它怎么回事！
Doug, if I'm not mistaken,
this place has got it going on!
I owe you big time for inviting me.
我欠你大的时候邀请我。
Who wants to dance?
I call this one the sprinkler.
谁愿意跳舞吗？
我称它是自动喷水灭火。
You think it would be okay to wear
this to your brother's wedding?
你认为它会好起来的穿
这对你哥哥的婚礼吗？
你哥哥的婚礼上，男人。
你打算怎么穿？
Your brother's wedding, man.
What are you gonna wear?
You have to hand it to Steve.
That Emily is the perfect woman.
你必须把它交给史蒂夫。
艾米莉是一个完美的女人。
Strong legs, tight stomach,
positive mental attitude...
壮腿，肚子紧，
积极的心态...
- 她真的可以让你的轨道上。
- 闭嘴..！ ldiot。
- She can really keep you on track.
- Shut up..! ldiot.
只是因为你和你的兄弟
有问题， -
Just because you and your brother
are having problems, -
- that's no reason to refer to my
intellect in a diminutive manner.
- 这是没有理由看我的
智力在一个身材矮小的方式。
I'm sorry. It's just...
对不起。这只是...
Can we not talk
about my brother for a second?
我们不能谈
我弟弟一秒钟？
- 1 0-4。边界集。
- 谢谢你。
- 10-4. Boundary set.
- Thank you.
I'm having a hell of a time.
我在的时候一个地狱。
At this moment, I want to make
a toast to Steve and Emily, -
在这一刻，我想使
举杯史蒂夫和Emily， -
- 后天谁
将先生和夫人史蒂芬Butabi。
- who after tomorrow
will be Mr. and Mrs. Steven Butabi.
- Emily Sanderson-Butabi.
- Whoever.
- 艾米莉桑德森-Butabi。
- 谁。
I would like to thank my parents,
who came in all the way from Maine.
我要感谢我的父母，
谁排在从缅因州一路。
- Despite Mom's sciatica.
- Terrific, sir.
- 尽管妈妈的坐骨神经痛。
- 太棒了，先生。
和Butabis，谁进来
从Yayman一路。
And the Butabis, who came in
all the way from Yayman.
- Yemen.
- And that's not the only union.
- 也门。
- 而这还不是唯一的工会。
- 我们得到了一个新的灯泡工厂店。
- 植物灯店。好多了。
- We got a new lamp-plant store.
- Plant-lamp store. Much better.
- Seriously, it sounds better.
- Steve?
- 说真的，这听起来更好。
- 史蒂夫？
You want to make a toast?
你想敬酒？
I think you should make a toast.
All the men are making toasts.
我觉得你应该做一个烤面包。
所有的男人都在祝酒词。
Okay, I just want to say,
"What's up, Grandma, Grandpa?"
好吧，我只想说，
“怎么了，奶奶，爷爷？”
和其他两位老人，
“怎么了？”
And to the other two old people,
"What's up?"
- Yeah, you.
- Very nice.
- 是啊，你。
- 很不错的。
Steve is thrilled
that this family's coming together.
史蒂夫非常高兴
这家的撞在了一起。
I'd like to show you some of our
business plans for after the merger.
我想向您展示一些我们的
业务计划，合并后。
Dad? ls there any way
we can cancel this whole thing?
爸爸？ LS有什么办法
我们可以取消这件事？
- Yes... No!
- That is so funny.
- 是的......不！
- 那是太有趣了。
But it's like Emily turned out to be
this whole different other person.
但它像艾米丽竟然是
这个完全不同的其他人。
让我来解释一下。
Let me explain something.
餐饮供应商已支付。
你的祖父母来了。
The caterer has been paid.
Your grandparents came.
所有的人都紧张
他们的婚礼的前一天晚上。
All men are nervous
the night before their wedding.
所有的球员都是那种紧张和
希望她吃肉毒中毒的可以吗？
All guys are nervous and kind of
hope she eats a can of botulism?
She could hang out with a deer and
accidentally be shot by a hunter.
她可以用鹿挂出，
不慎被猎人被枪毙。
You know, when she's sleeping she
makes that nose whistle sound, -
你知道，当她睡觉，她
使该鼻鸣笛声， -
- and you want to ram her toothbrush
up her nostril into her skull.
- 你想猛撞她的牙刷
她的鼻孔入她的头骨。
These are perfectly normal feelings.
这是完全正常的感情。
Doug, are you there? It's Steve.
道格，你在吗？这是史蒂夫。
Hi, you've reached Doug Butabi.
I'm outside living it up.
嗨，你已经达到了道格Butabi。
我在外面活起来。
Unlike my pussywhipped brother -
我不像pussywhipped哥哥 -
- who's too busy throwing his life away
for Emily. Beep.
- 谁也管不了扔寻欢
艾米丽。哔声。
Doug? Sorry I missed you.
I guess I'm getting married -
道格？对不起，我错过了你。
我想我要结婚了 -
- and I'm just wondering
if you wanted to be my best man.
- 我只是想知道
如果你想成为我的伴郎。
给我打电话或页面我。
Give me a call or page me.
I'm in our room still
across from the pool.
我在我们的房间还
对面的游泳池。
见到你。
See you.
- Let's go over this one more time.
- I know my duties as best man.
- 让我们来过这一次。
- 我知道我的职责伴郎。
I walk down the aisle.
I stand next to you.
我走在过道。
我就站在你旁边。
- I settle interwedding skirmishes.
- No, no...
- 我解决interwedding小规模冲突。
- 不，不......
You're the best man. Not the wedding
bouncer. You just back me up.
你是最好的男人。没有婚礼
保镖。你只是我的支援。
一样，如果事情变得太沉重，
我踩在像去污剂。
Like, if things get too heavy,
I step in like a spotter.
- 是的，没错。
- 谢谢，伙计。
- Yeah, right.
- Thanks, man.
让我们去。我们准备好了，我们走吧。
Let's go. We're ready, let's go.
Do you want your kid blessed or not?
你想你的孩子祝福或没有？
- 理查德GRIECO。你知道史蒂夫？
- 我只是不想被起诉。
- Richard Grieco. You know Steve?
- I just don't want to be sued.
No, listen to me. You can't get your
kid confirmed for less than $150.
不，听我说。你不能让你的
孩子确诊为低于1美元50。
You want your kid blessed,
you call me.
您希望您的孩子有福了，
你给我打电话。
Dad, I didn't have a bachelor party.
That's a major part of a wedding.
爸爸，我没有一个单身派对。
这是一个婚礼的重要组成部分。
因此，我们可以延迟几个小时
这样我们就可以去一家脱衣舞俱乐部？
So could we delay a couple of hours
so that we could go to a strip club?
I have to go. Leave me a message.
我得走了。给我留言。
哎...史蒂夫结婚。
你是男人！
Hey... Steve getting married.
You're the man!
闭嘴，克雷格。我走
在过道，你家伙！
Shut up, Craig. I'm walking
down the aisle, you dick!
我告诉你穿白色的。
奶奶的，下车的手机。
I told you to wear white.
Grandma, get off the phone.
Dearly beloved. We're gathered
here today to join...
亲爱的。我们正在收集
今天在这里参加...
Did we already start? Oh.
我们是否已经开始？呵呵。
我觉得有所谓
是一个蜂鸣器或口哨什么的。
I thought there was supposed
to be a buzzer or a whistle or something.
......这个人倾其
和这位女士的神圣的婚姻殿堂。
... to join together this man
and this woman in holy matrimony.
But first I understand the bride and
groom have each prepared something.
但首先，我明白了新娘和
新郎各有准备的东西。
“亲爱的史蒂夫。他们说，如果你设置
免费的东西，它回来 -
"Dear Steve. They say if you set
something free and it comes back -
- you should love it forever.
Like one of your silk plants, -
- 你应该爱它，直到永远。
像你们的丝绸厂之一， -
- I'll try to stay beautiful. I know
our lives together will be great."
- 我会尽力保持美丽。我知道
我们生活在一起将是巨大的。“
"Just like when we saw David
Copperfield on our first date."
当我们看到大卫“一样，
科波菲尔在我们的第一次约会。“
"Love Emily."
“爱蜜莉。”
“我曾经看到外面你
我父亲的商店 -
"I used to see you outside
my father's store -
- 然后我们去上一些日期
你让我和你做爱。“
- and then we went on some dates
and you let me have sex with you."
Oh, I'm done.
哦，我完成了。
If anyone has reason to believe
that this man or woman -
如果任何人有理由相信
这个男人还是女人 -
- should not be married, speak now
or forever hold your peace.
- 不应该结婚的，现在说话
或永远握住你的平安。
- What's up? From out of town?
- Don't hit on the bridesmaid.
- 这是怎么回事？从外地来的？
- 不要打的伴娘。
- It's your wedding.
- Wait till after the ceremony.
- 这是你结婚。
- 等到仪式结束后。
Do you promise to love Emily for
as long as you both shall live?
你承诺的爱艾米莉的
只要你们两个人就要活了？
我爸爸已经支付的餐饮服务商。
My dad already paid the caterer.
你承诺的爱史蒂芬的
只要你们两个人就要活了？
Do you promise to love Steven for
as long as you both shall live?
- 以后我史蒂芬，重复。
- 在我之后。
- Steven, repeat after me.
- After me.
- With this ring, I thee wed.
- 有了这个戒指，我娶你。
Now, Emily.
现在，艾米丽。
With this ring...
有了这个戒指...
Doug!
道格！
- 什么是地狱的，他来这里干什么？
- 让他停下来。
- What the hell's he doing here?
- Make him stop.
打开音乐关闭！
Turn that music off!
You know
what I paid for this wedding?
你知道吗
我为此付出了婚礼？
Don't do that with your head.
That's so dumb!
不这样做，你的脑袋。
这是如此愚蠢！
- Mr. Butabi, I can't...
- Keep going. You want to get paid?
- Butabi先生，我不能...
- 继续下去。你要得到报酬？
- You're out of my will!
- I told you he was a jerk!
- 你离开我的意志！
- 我告诉你他是个混蛋！
艾米莉...对不起。我还没想好。
Emily... Sorry. I'm not ready yet.
- 史蒂夫，停！
- 尼斯诗，虽然。对不起，爸爸。
- Steve, stop!
- Nice poem, though. Sorry, Dad.
Steve, come back here!
Don't you leave me. I'm not kidding.
史蒂夫，回来这里！
不要你离开我。我不是在开玩笑。
Mr. Butabi, as an actor and observer
of human nature, I can tell you -
Butabi先生，作为一个演员和观察员
人性的，我可以告诉你 -
- that your son is not ready
for this sort of commitment.
- 你的儿子还没有准备好
对于这种承诺。
- Hello.
- Hey.
- 你好。
- 嘿。
- 来吧，爸爸。
- 你在做什么？
- Go ahead, Father.
- What are you doing?
艾米丽，史蒂夫的纪律缺乏
这是他对你表示感谢。
Emily, Steve's discipline is lacking
as is his appreciation for you.
现在，我可以卧推305磅，
和自己的身体脂肪是小于2％。
Now, I can bench press 305 pound,
and my body fat is less than 2%.
I am a professional trainer. I also
hope to market my own protein bar.
我是一名专业培训师。我也
希望向市场推出自己的蛋白质吧。
Plus, I've always loved you.
另外，我一直都爱着你。
Okay. But we should
look into infomercials.
好吧。但是，我们应该
直视电视购物节目。
- This is a completely new fee. Cool?
- Yeah.
- 这是一个完全新的费用。酷？
- 是啊。
好吧。亲爱的，
我们今天在这里聚集了......
Okay. Dearly beloved,
we're gathered here again today...
另外，我把克雷格泡吧。
Also, I took Craig clubbing.
这是所有权利。
That was all right.
另外，我租了很多视频。
我没有做什么其他东西。
Plus I rented a lot of videos.
I didn't do much else.
Look, Steve...
瞧，史蒂夫...
I'm sorry.
I said a lot of bad things before.
对不起。
我说了很多不好的事情之前。
I've been thinking...
You're my brother.
我一直在想...
你是我的兄弟。
We're brothers,
and when we're together...
我们是兄弟，
而当我们在一起...
我只是...
I just...
You don't drag me down.
你不要拖我失望。
我拖我失望。
I drag me down.
And you...
而你...
You complete me.
你完成了我。
- Shut up.
- What?
- 闭嘴。
- 什么？
Just shut up.
You had me at "hello".
闭上你的嘴。
你让我在“你好”。
LT在我看来，你是一个有点困难
道格上比你在史蒂夫。
lt seems to me, you're a bit harder
on Doug than you are on Steve.
It's true. It's just that Doug is
so rebellious. I can't control him.
这是真的。这只是道格是
这样叛逆。我无法控制他。
But rebellious, scrappy, dreamer...
但叛逆，斗志旺盛，梦想家...
What other young man
does that remind you of?
还有什么其他的年轻人
这是否提醒你？
- MyseIf as a kid.
- So who are you really fighting with?
- MyseIf作为一个孩子。
- 那么，谁是你真正的战斗？
GRIECO先生...
你看穿我。
Mr. Grieco...
You see right through me.
我错过了这辆车。
我看好它。
I missed this car.
I look good in it.
你看看也不错。
And you look good also.
Thanks.
Glad you moved back into the room.
谢谢。
很高兴你搬回了房间。
Dad was cool about the wedding
after his chat with Grieco.
爸爸是凉爽关于婚礼
之后他聊天GRIECO。
And it really improved
your relationship with him.
它真的改善
你跟他的关系。
- ls that an outside nightclub?
- That's your idea.
- LS的外部夜总会？
- 那是你的想法。
拉了过来。让我们来一探究竟。
Pull over. Let's check it out.
- We only let people in on the list.
- We're on the list.
- 我们只让人们在名单上。
- 我们的名单上。
- Steve and Doug Butabi.
- Step right in.
- 史蒂夫和道格Butabi。
- 步骤正确英寸
- Go right in.
- I guess we should go in then.
- 向右走英寸
- 我想我们应该去的呢。
- We're gonna go in.
- We're going in.
I can't believe we got in.
Sure it wasn't a mistake?
我不能相信我们上了车。
肯定这是不是一个错误？
- 这是奇怪的是在这里。
- 但是，他们偷了你的想法。
- It's weird to be in here.
- But they stole your idea.
Butabis? I've been looking
all over for you. Come here!
- Mr. Zadir!
- How do you like our club?
- Our club?
- I cut you in. lt was your idea.
- 甜蜜的屁股甜蜜。
- 跑步俱乐部是艰苦的工作。
- Sweet ass sweet.
- Running a club is hard work.
- Don't worry about it.
- We're workaholics.
- 不要担心。
- 我们是工作狂。
Dooey just called from Pismo Beach.
He says he didn't grab your ass.
Dooey从庇斯摩海滩刚刚打电话。
他说，他并没有抢你的屁股。
What is he up to now?
什么是他到现在？
- 噢，我的上帝！
- Oh, my God!
- Let's do some business.
- All right.
- 让我们做一些生意。
- 好吧。
- Put some cherries on that.
- Nice call.
- 放在一些樱桃。
- 尼斯电话。
- Mr. Butabi, can you approve this?
- That looks fine and all that.
- Butabi先生，你能同意吗？
- 这看起来很好，这一切。
- Hi, Mr. Barntabi.
- It's Butabi, but that's okay.
How's the hair?
Successful-club-owner good?
That voice sounds so familiar.
这声音听起来很熟悉。
- 你是...？
- 道格？
- Are you..?
- Doug?
- 信用狐狸精？
- 我的上帝，我不能相信这一点。
- Credit vixen?
- My God, I can't believe this.
You're even more beautiful
than you sound.
你更美丽
比你的声音。
- You stopped calling.
- Not because I didn't want to.
- 你不再打电话。
- 不是因为我不想。
Am I what you expected?
我是什么令您满意？
I totally approve.
我完全赞同。
- You're not here with anyone?
- Just my friend.
- 你不是这里的人？
- 只是我的朋友。
Hottie police officer?
辣妹警官吗？
我真的很期待
至6月6日与您会面在法庭上。
I was really looking forward
to meeting you in court on June 6th.
- So, do you guys wanna dance?
- No.
- 那么，你们想跳舞吗？
- 号
- 是的。
- Yes.
- 哦，我喜欢这首歌。
- 我得到的是种病态。
- Oh, I love this song.
- I'm getting kind of sick of it.
I broke the window again.